Contact

joy.aytona@gmail.com joy.aytona@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/joydaytona (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Acute Care

Critical Care

Languages

Tagalog (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Elementary) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Sexual Assault Nurse Examiner Training

Joy Aytona

Corrections RN at Colorado Department of Corrections Canon City, Colorado

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Staff Coordination/Employee Health, Nursing Management, Neuro-Oncology, Emergency, Medicine, Performance Data Analysis, Core Measures Abstraction, Healthcare Risk Management, Infection Control, Dialysis, Quality Control and Management.

Certified in Sex Crimes Investigations in North Carolina, Forensic Pathology:Death Investigations at the University of North Dakota, Sexual Assault Nurse Examiner Trainee in the State of Utah. Background in Computer Forensics and Drug- Facilitated Sexual Assault.

Strong healthcare services professional working in a Master's degree focused in Forensic Psychology Licensure Track from The Chicago School of Professional Psychology.

Experience

Colorado Department of Corrections Corrections RN July 2020 - Present (1 month) Canon City, Colorado, United States

The Chicago School of Professional Psychology Research Specialist (Remote) February 2020 - Present (6 months) Los Angeles, California, United States

Indian Health Service Clinical Nurse Coordinator @ Indian Health Services -DHHS July 2016 - March 2020 (3 years 9 months)

Fort Duschene, Utah

TravelMax/Raleigh Central Prison

Dept. of Public Safety, NC - Corrections RN (Raleigh Central Prison) - contract

January 2015 - July 2015 (7 months)

Raleigh, NC

Charge RN

TravelMax

RN, Corrections, Varner Unit Supermax All-Male Correctional Facility-contract

October 2014 - January 2015 (4 months)

TravelMax, Maury Correctional Facility - Closed Security RN, Corrections- contract
June 2014 - September 2014 (4 months)
Maury, NC

Nurse Core, St. Petersburg, Florida Travel RN-ER, Home Health IV RN (Per Diem) November 2012 - October 2013 (1 year) St Petersburg, FL

Palms of Pasadena Hospital (IASIS Healthcare), St. Petersburg, Florida

Core Measures Abstractor and QAPI Analyst June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

South Pasadena, FL

Cypress Health Group of St. Petersburg, Florida
Director of Risk Management and Performance Improvement
January 2013 - June 2013 (6 months)

St. Petersburg, FL

St. Anthony's Hospital, St. Petersburg, Florida CN II RN - Emergency Services June 2012 - October 2012 (5 months) St. Petersburg, Fl

CN II, ER RN

Duke University Health System Clinical Nurse Educator/Coordinator - Epilepsy/Sleep Disorders May 2011 - June 2012 (1 year 2 months)

Neurosciences and Spine Center/ Seizures/Epilepsy and Sleep Clinic

Duke University Health System - Durham, North Carolina Registered Nurse- BSN

February 2010 - January 2011 (1 year)

Registered Nurse, Stroke, Neuro-Oncology Unit/Medicine/Palliative

Select Specialty Hospital-Saginaw, Michigan Charge Registered Nurse/Staff Registered Nurse August 2005 - December 2009 (4 years 5 months)

CAPITOL MEDICAL CENTER

4 years 1 month

Charge Registered Nurse/Staff Registered Nurse Emergency Room January 2001 - January 2005 (4 years 1 month)

Manila, Philippines

Staff Registered Nurse

January 2001 - January 2002 (1 year 1 month)

Medical-Surgical Unit, OB/GYN Ward, Pediatrics Unit and General Ward.

METRO CAVITE DIALYSIS CENTER

Staff Dialysis Registered Nurse January 2000 - January 2001 (1 year 1 month)

.

Manila Doctors Hospital Staff Registered Nurse, ICU January 1998 - January 1999 (1 year 1 month)

Education

The Chicago School of Professional Psychology

Master's degree, Forensic Psychology Licensure Track (2018 - 2022)

The University of North Dakota School of Medicine and Health Sciences

Forensic Pathology: Death Investigations · (2015 - 2016)

International Association of Forensic Nurses SANE A/P, SART · (2014 - 2015)

Argosy University School of Psychology

MA Forensic Psychology Non-licensure Track · (2013 - 2015)

North Carolina Justice Academy, Edneyville Campus Certificate, Sex Crimes Investigations, Drug-facilitated Sexual Assault · (2014 - 2014)